# **Antonio Lee**

Phone: 408-857-8257

Email: antoniolee@outlook.com Web: antoniolee.github.io

GitHub: http://github.com/antoniolee

LinkedIn: <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/pub/antonio-lee/61/196/351">http://www.linkedin.com/pub/antonio-lee/61/196/351</a>

### **Summary**

I am a software developer who enjoys creating new forms of interactive media, games and web development. I focus on user interaction, user experience and everything design oriented, but I'm a quick learner and like to help in all aspects of development when possible. When I'm not developing software, you can find me skateboarding, making music, rock climbing, taking photos, sight seeing and/or traveling with friends.

Skills		
Web Development	Game Development	Software & Utilities
HTML5 / CSS3 / LESS	Lua / Corona SDK	Adobe Photoshop / Illustrator
Javascript / JQuery.js / Bootstrap.js	Java / Android SDK	Git / Github
Python / web2py	C# / XNA 4.0	Ableton / Music Production
Vagrant / LAMP	Agile Development w/ Scrum	Google Docs (Word/Excel/PPT)

#### Work Experience

Undergraduate Researcher in Education and Web Development University of California, Santa Cruz October 2013 – June 2014 Santa Cruz, California

- Created two interactive web applications for two different studies under a professor at University of California, Santa Cruz and Gargani + Company (http://www.gcoinc.com/), funded by the National Science Foundation (NSF)
  - NSF Sortable:

http://antoniolee.pythonanywhere.com/NSF Sortable

- A web application which generates a unique list of four generated teacher name cards which have different statistics represented by a bar graph and a picture of their face to match. The user rates the teacher by sorting the name cards in ascending order from most to least qualified. Results are stored into a database where information can be drawn out and findings/connections can be made.
- Math Performance Predictor:

http://antoniolee.pythonanywhere.com/NSFUCSC

- Generates a bar graph which depicts predicted standardized math score statistics of students from 3<sup>rd</sup> – 8<sup>th</sup> grade depending on three variables which users can adjust. User accounts can be made and personal results can be recorded into a database.
- Created web layouts and designs for websites using Bootstrap.js
- Created graph & name card generator using JQplot.js, jquery.js, python & Web2py
- Created database to store data & results, user information & accounts, using SQLite and Web2py

Private Tutor Merit World September 2013 – January 2014 Santa Cruz, California

- Private tutor helping high school seniors with the fundamentals of web design.
- Help to create online portfolios and/or websites using wordpress.com or HTML / CSS

Web Developer / Graphic Design Intern Cubico Media Labs LLC June 2013 – September 2013 San Jose, California

- Used Photoshop & Illustrator to create web banners, graphics, t-shirt designs
- Used Photoshop to create different layouts and wireframes for Tres Royale's E-Commerce website
- Created an E-Commerce website for Tres Royale with responsive design using HTML/CSS/Bootstrap.js

Prep Cook / Counter Jake's of Saratoga

June 2011 – August 2013 Saratoga, California

Made gourmet pizzas and handled ovens. Took orders at the register, helped open and close restaurant.

Prep Cook
The Garret of Campbell

August 2009 – June 2011 Campbell, California

Made gourmet pizzas and handled ovens. Took orders at the register, helped open and close restaurant.

## Game Development

CMPS 170-172: Game Design Sequence 1,2,3 Game Title: Now We're Cooking! September 2013 – June 2014

http://nwcgame.com

- Now We're Cooking is a mobile game for Android and iOS devices. The story takes place in a reality cooking TV show in which the host has turned all the food evil. You now must utilize there chef powers to combine food by swiping different ingredients together, before it's too late. Food comes down in three different lanes, your job is to adjust lane speeds and create food by swiping food together.
- Roles: Lead Producer, Programmer, Artist and Audio Lead

CMPS 20: Game Design Experience

January 2012 – March 2012

Game Title: Solar Crysis (CMPS 20 Sammy's Winner)

http://games.soe.ucsc.edu/project/solar-crysis/

- Solar Crysis is a twin-stick shooter where the player controls a "nanobot" whose job is to constantly repair a continuously breaking solar panel. The solar panel is the playing field, when a panel is broken the nanobot can no longer cross the panel. The game has a choice/consequence aspect to it, where the nanobot can either protect itself from enemies or repair the solar panel, not both at the same time. Created using XNA 4.0 and C#.
- Roles: Lead Designer, Programmer, Artist

#### Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science: Game Design University of California, Santa Cruz

GPA: 3.0

Santa Cruz, California September 2010 – June 2014